<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <generator>RSS Builder by B!Soft</generator>
    <title>0ekekddddd site updates</title>
    <link>https://0ekekddddd.github.io/</link>
    <description />
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <copyright>sam @ 0ekekddddd</copyright>
    <item>
      <title>2025.06.02 // Visitors Of Sidbury Bank</title>
      <pubDate>Mon, 2 Jun 2025 10:54:42 -0500</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>New blogpost redeeming my bragging rights in Identity V's costume gacha.</p>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2025.05.27 // Many updates, many updates! Please read.</title>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 15:20:59 -0500</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Sorry for the radio silence everyone. I can officially announce that I'll be attending Tokyo X @ NRG Park in Houston, TX as a vendor. Speaking of artist branding, I've opted for URL twofold squatting; Gristlepod and Texas Kiss Rhinestone/TKR/K. Rhinestone. <a href="https://gristlepod.github.io">Gristlepod.github.io</a> is solely business (however "un-personal" my raunchy stash of Luchino pin-ups can be).</p>
<p>To celebrate my new extreme act of selfhood, I re-published my fashion blog with many pictures of myself and reformatted the Luchino Diruse Shrinepage (now renamed "Glaciale Undertones"). For those into both Luchino Diruse and fashion, a log about my itabag is available under <a href="https://0ekekddddd.github.io/jfashion/itabag.html">TKR fashion</a>.</p>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2025.04.06 // quitter's park: twitch stream</title>
      <pubDate>Sun, 6 Apr 2025 02:35:21 -0500</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>I've been silent streaming on Twitch and it's been a very repairing experience to directly chat with followers and friends. Although they come and go in small numbers with large periods of silence inbetween, I get to host a space where I can share my music tastes and I've merged a little closer into my established community.</p>
<p>I whipped up an <a href="https://0ekekddddd.github.io/stream/" target="_parent">onsite mount</a>  to watch my streams from. Drop by 2pm - 4am CST and chat with me.</p>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2025.03.01 // another luchino fansite update</title>
      <pubDate>Sat, 1 Mar 2025 00:42:53 -0600</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>A photo gallery section was added subsectioned under Entrance.</p>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2025.02.19 // luchino fansite update</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 11:02:36 -0600</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>The Luchino fansite should be bracing a new layout theme along with new subsections, "Music Playlist," and "Merchandise I Collected." They pretty much explain themselves; just expect them to be updated for as long as I upkeep the site. I've taken a liking to writing in my free time when I'm spending time with my girlfriend or not overhauling other dev projects, so chances are a "Fanfiction" tab will&nbsp;make its way in.</p>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2025.02.10 // "Why You Should Make A Website"</title>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 21:16:58 -0600</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Rehashing the collapse of the centric web and how web design plays a part in the scam. Building healthy habits such as migrating&nbsp;to independent platforms and building a website&nbsp;might help you.</p>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2025.02.06 // "Refléter Op. 6", RSS feed applied</title>
      <pubDate>Thu, 6 Feb 2025 18:35:57 -0600</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>several graphic changes were applied to the site and some directories were recategorized for the following update. i've set up two rss feeds respectively for my personal blog and store. the landing page will now display the newest posts of both feeds. </p>
<p>posted&nbsp;an&nbsp;identity v&nbsp;fanfiction "<a href="https://0ekekddddd.github.io/log/fanfic/refleterop6">Refléter Op. 6</a>" that i've written some time ago in personal log &gt; fanfiction.</p>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2024.12.22 // spreadsheet redeco</title>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 18:31:04 -0600</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>touched up the music page and sorted my spreadsheet archive to be used globally rather than page by page. cleaned up luchino's shrine.</p>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2024.09.06 // church of luchino</title>
      <pubDate>Fri, 6 Sep 2024 18:25:09 -0600</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>edited on 2025.2.6. date of when the church of luchino was published.</p>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2024.08.24 // general website-itry</title>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 18:17:49 -0600</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>site changes are officially being recorded... i might have waited too long to do this ever since the host switch. a brand new sitewide layout graphic has been applied for the special occasion, but i'll keep using the old one for the blog. regarding ko-fi i've come across issues with overseas sales, so i'll issue a list of countries i can't ship to internationally in the upcoming commission TOS.</p>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>